<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>intro on TWIST</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in intro on TWIST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About TWIST</title>
      <link>/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>As part of the 2018 Swiss Statistics Meeting, hackdays will be held for the first time. During the hackdays, interested participants will research the potential of various data sets. The attendeees will work together in interdisciplinary teams to explore the data and master the challenges. The different skills and backgrounds within the different teams will allow for creativity and the development of new solutions and ideas. Free participation &amp;amp; family-friendly setting Participation in the hackdays is free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Statistics Meeting 2018</title>
      <link>/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>While statistics is an exact science, emotions by contrast are subjective, often irrational and difficult to measure. Despite or perhaps even due to this contrast, statistics and emotions are increasingly considered together: if moods and feelings increasingly define what is true and false, what exactly is the role of statistics?
 Are decisions too often made on a purely emotional basis, neglecting statistical data and proven facts?
 How important are evidence-based decision processes given that factual correctness is becoming less and less relevant in politics and the economy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a group of people working for organizations committed to bringing together different communities to show the benefits of open data and encourage the adoption of open data policies.
Organization Committee Marco Sieber &amp;amp; Reto Wick (OpenData Stadt Zürich) / Andreas Amsler, Matthias Mazenauer &amp;amp; Thomas Lo Russo (Statistisches Amt Kanton Zürich) / Christina Sarasua, University of Zurich &amp;amp; Wikimedia Foundation / Gonzalo Casas, Open Network Infrastructure Network Association / Muriel Buri &amp;amp; Dorothea Hug Peter, University of Zurich &amp;amp; R User-Group</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>