<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TWIST</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TWIST</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 14:41:19 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>housing market activity over space and time</title>
      <link>/post/real_estate_zh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 14:41:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/real_estate_zh/</guid>
      <description>The events on the real estate market are followed meticulously by many. No wonder that the property transfer statistics are among the top sought-after statistical data sets in the Canton of Zurich. At the TWIST-hackdays, for the first time, an open test-data set that includes all real estate transactions in the period 2010-2014 is being made available to the public.
You get a first-time opportunity to work with a high-resolution spatial dataset of real estate trades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three stories about a child</title>
      <link>/post/three_stories/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/three_stories/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you are a 6 year old child. And you plan to live in a cozy neighborhood in the wonderful city of Basel. Your first day of school will be on Monday – how exciting! But first you have to find a place to live&amp;hellip; Imagine further, that you have a decent flair for open statistical data (under open use license) and quite a talent for programming. So you are probably the first ever kid on this world that is able to code before even being able to write in his mother tongue – how weird… But hey, it’s all about imagination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a close look at the traffic</title>
      <link>/post/traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/traffic/</guid>
      <description>We know Zurich&amp;rsquo;s data of automated pedestrian and bicycle counting quite well. Together with you we would like to find out if and how it can be compared with analogous data of other cities and / or means of transport. What patterns come to light when combining Zurich&amp;rsquo;s foot and bicycle frequencies with VBZ or SBB data? How high is the share of people going to the train station by bike?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatial statistics at TWIST2018</title>
      <link>/post/spatial_statistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 14:41:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/spatial_statistics/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered in which areas of the canton of Zurich the population is the youngest? Or where the density of employees in a certain industry is the highest? How many people live and work in your neighbourhood? The spatial statistics layers in the cantonal GIS-Browser bear the answers.
Soon, they will be made available as open data via API. As a premiere, for the occasion of the TWIST-Hackdays, preview datasets are made available!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give your address a position. Give your position an address.</title>
      <link>/post/opengeocoder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/opengeocoder/</guid>
      <description>Geocoding and reverse geocoding Addresses represent an important reference dataset for data analyses. In the GIS domain addresses are the essential basis for customer- and business analyses. Addresses are also pervasive on the web. When we search for directions on google maps we use addresses: behind the scene, these addresses are converted to geographic coordinates, which are then used for the routing analysis. Now the other way around. When we click on a street in google maps we get a tooltip showing the address information of that location: behind the scene, geographic coordinates are converted to addresses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsourced open data from «Züri wie neu»</title>
      <link>/post/zueri_wie_neu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/zueri_wie_neu/</guid>
      <description>While we strive to publish as many interesting new open data for TWIST as possible, it is worth taking a look at already existing open data. In this post we would like to give you a brief outlook over the crowdsourced open data from the application «Züri wie neu». There might still be some hidden, so far undiscovered, truths to be found in it.
The application and derived open data «Züri wie neu» is an online platform of the Zurich city administration in order to facilitate the reporting of damaged infrastructure by citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three steps from data desert to a thriving data ecosystem</title>
      <link>/post/three_steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/three_steps/</guid>
      <description>Isolated data is information dryland. Data needs to be rooted in its context to blossom and if we want it to thrive, data needs to live in a networked ecosystem.
First step: Let the data sprout For data to sprout, it has to be available to everyone to access, use and share. At TWIST2018 we work with Open Data. And we want to work with you, to find innovative ways to analyse, visualise and combine data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring insight into public finances</title>
      <link>/post/public_finances/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/public_finances/</guid>
      <description>How are public services financed? Where does my tax-money go? Which claims around public spending generally considered valid are facts, which are myths? Help us getting sense of public finances, unveil hidden patterns and opening up public financial accounts to a broader public by analyzing and visualizing open data.
Get your hands on open spending data at the TWIST-Hackdays! Since 1990, the expenditures of Zurich&amp;rsquo;s municipalities have been in step with those of the canton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The «Ideas &amp; Resources» web-page is live!</title>
      <link>/post/ideas_page_live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ideas_page_live/</guid>
      <description>We are currently collecting ideas and compiling a list of exciting data sets to be used at the Twist-Hackdays. There will be no prescribed challenges. We will provide a pool of ideas which will serve as a source of inspiration and a solid starting point for potential Hackday-projects. We do our best to make until yet undisclosed data sources open soon, which could be used for the first time at the TWIST-Hackdays.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>